car.info 2014-12-20

# Privacy Policy | WebCorp

There are many different ways you can use our services - to search for and share information, to communicate with other people or to create new content. When you share information with us, for example by creating a WebCorp Account, we can make those services even better - to show you more relevant content, to help you connect with people, to make sharing with others quicker and easier. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we're using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

Your privacy matters to us so please take the time to get to know our practices - and if you have any questions [contact us](http://webcorp.com/contact/).

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users - from figuring out basic stuff like which country in which you're located, to more complex things like which people matter most to you online.

We collect information in two ways:

  * Information you give us. For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a WebCorp Account. When you do, we'll ask for personal information, like your email address. When you create a WebCorp Account, we automatically create a publicly visible profile, which may include some or all of the content you post on our website.
  * Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you interact with other WebCorp users or content. This information includes:
    * Device information

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). We may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your WebCorp Account.

    * Log information

When you use our services or view content provided by WebCorp, we may automatically collect and store certain information in our server logs. This may include:

      * details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
      * Internet protocol address (i.e. IP address).
      * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your WebCorp Account.
  * Location information

When you use a location-enabled WebCorp service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device.

  * Local storage

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

  * Cookies and anonymous identifiers

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit WebCorp, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with our partner's services, such as Google advertising and analytical services.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect WebCorp and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content - like giving you customized content.

We may use the name you provide for your WebCorp Profile across all of the services we offer that require a WebCorp Account. If other users already have your email, or other information that identifies you, we may show them your publicly visible WebCorp Profile information, such as your name and photo.

When you contact WebCorp, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. We will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health.

We may combine personal information from one service with information, including personal information, from other WebCorp services - for example to make it easier to share things with people you know.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

## Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. For example, you can:

  * Review and control certain types of information tied to your WebCorp Account by going to your settings page.
  * Change your email and communication preferences by going to your notifications settings page.

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it's important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, we may not remember your basic login credentials which expedite future logins.

## Information you share

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

## Accessing and updating your personal information

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it - unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of WebCorp unless one of the following circumstances apply:

  * With your consent

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of WebCorp when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

  * For external processing

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * For legal reasons

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of WebCorp if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable [Terms of Use](http://webcorp.com/terms/), including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of WebCorp, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners - like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

If WebCorp is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information security

We work hard to protect WebCorp and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

  * We encrypt many of our services using SSL.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to WebCorp employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by WebCorp and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you on WebCorp, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self-regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

## Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).

 _Last Revised: June 15, 2014_
